<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="console-application">
  <id>org.kde.symmy</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSymmyxx</name>
  <summary>Frontend for the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Frontal per a la funcionalitat d'encriptatge simètric del GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Frontal per a la funcionalitat d'encriptatge simètric del GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Frontend for the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Frontend voor de symmetrische versleutelingsfunctionaliteit van GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Interface para a funcionalidade de encriptação simétrica do GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Frontend pre dynamické šifrovanie GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Gränssnitt för den symmetriska krypteringsfunktionaliteten i GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Оболонка до можливостей з симетричного шифрування у GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxFrontend for the symmetric encryption functionality of GPGxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Symmy is a simple command-line application that nicely wraps the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Symmy és una aplicació senzilla de línia d'ordres que embolcalla la funcionalitat d'encriptatge simètric del GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Symmy és una aplicació senzilla de línia d'ordes que embolcalla la funcionalitat d'encriptatge simètric del GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Symmy is a simple command-line application that nicely wraps the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Symmy is een eenvoudige commandoregel toepassing die de symmetrische versleutelingsfunctionaliteit van GPG omvat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Symmy é uma aplicação simples da linha de comandos que envolve de forma amigável a funcionalidade de encriptação do GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Symmy je jednoduchá konzolová aplikácia ktorá pekne zalomí symetrickú funkcionalitu GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Symmy är ett enkelt kommandoradsprogram som omsluter den symmetriska krypteringsfunktionaliteten i GPG på ett snyggt sätt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Symmy — проста програма із інтерфейсом командного рядка, яка є зручною обгорткою до функціональних можливостей із симетричного шифрування GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSymmy is a simple command-line application that nicely wraps the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG.xx</p>
    <p>Symmy also provides integration with GUI file managers such as Dolphin (Encrypt and Decrypt context menu actions), as well as integration with Plasma notifications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Symmy també proporciona la integració amb els gestors de fitxers IGU com el Dolphin (accions de menú contextual Encripta i Desencripta), així com la integració amb les notificacions del Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Symmy també proporciona la integració amb els gestors de fitxers IGU com el Dolphin (accions de menú contextual Encripta i Desencripta), així com la integració amb les notificacions del Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Symmy also provides integration with GUI file managers such as Dolphin (Encrypt and Decrypt context menu actions), as well as integration with Plasma notifications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Symmy biedt ook integratie met GUI bestandsbeheerders zoals Dolphin (versleuteling- en ontcijferingacties in het contextmenu), evenals integratie met Plasma-meldingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Symmy também oferece a integração com os gestor de ficheiros gráficos, como o  Dolphin (acções do menu de contexto 'Encriptar' e 'Descodificar'), assim como a integração com as notificações do Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Symmy poskytuje aj integráciu s GUI súborovými správcami ako Dolphin (kontextové akcie šifrovanie a dešifrovanie) ako aj integráciu s Plasma pripomienkami.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Symmy erbjuder också integrering med grafiska filhanterare som Dolphin (sammanhangsberoende menyalternativ Kryptera och Avkryptera), samt integrering med underrättelser i Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У Symmy передбачено можливості інтеграції до програм із графічним інтерфейсом для керування файлами, зокрема Dolphin (пункти контекстного меню «Зашифрувати» і «Розшифрувати»), а також інтеграцію із системою сповіщень Плазми.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSymmy also provides integration with GUI file managers such as Dolphin (Encrypt and Decrypt context menu actions), as well as integration with Plasma notifications.xx</p>
    <p>You can track the progress of an encryption/decryption job or kill it, using the notifications plasmoid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Podeu seguir el progrés d'un treball d'encriptatge/desencriptatge o matar-lo, usant el plasmoide de les notificacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Podeu seguir el progrés d'un treball d'encriptatge/desencriptatge o matar-lo, usant el plasmoide de les notificacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">You can track the progress of an encryption/decryption job or kill it, using the notifications plasmoid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U kunt de voortgang van een taak voor versleutelen/ontcijferen volgen of afbreken, met de plasmoid voor meldingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Poderá seguir a evolução de uma tarefa de encriptação/descodificação ou interrompê-la, usando o plasmóide de notificações.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Môžete sledovať priebeh šifrovania a dešifrovania alebo úlohu zrušiť pomocou plazmoidu notifikácií.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Förloppet för krypterings- eller avkrypteringsjobb går att följa och de kan avbrytas med Plasmoiden för underrättelser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ви зможете стежити за поступом завдання із шифрування або розшифровування і переривати його за допомогою плазмоїда сповіщень.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxYou can track the progress of an encryption/decryption job or kill it, using the notifications plasmoid.xx</p>
  </description>
  <provides>
    <binary>symmy</binary>
  </provides>
  <update_contact>elvis.angelaccio_at_kde.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
