<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
    SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2017 Elvis Angelaccio <elvis.angelaccio@kde.org>
-->
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.symmy</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin</extends>
  <name>Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSymmyxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Symmy</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Symmy</name>
  <summary>Frontend for the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Frontal per a la funcionalitat d'encriptatge simètric del GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Frontal per a la funcionalitat d'encriptació simètrica de GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Rozhraní pro symetrickou funkčnost šifrování GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Benutzeroberfläche für die symmetrische GPG-Verschlüsselung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Περιβάλλον χρήσης για τη λειτουργία συμμετρικής κρυπτογραφίας του GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Frontend for the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Fasado por la simetria ĉifrada funkcieco de GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Interfaz para la función de cifrado simétrico de GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">GPG sümmeetrilise krüptimise võimaluse kasutajaliides</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">GPGren zifratze simetrikoaren funtzionaltasunerako aurrealdekoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">GPG:n symmetrisen salauksen käyttöliittymä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Interface pour les fonctionnalités de chiffrement symétrique de « GPG »</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Interface para a funcionalidade de cifraxe simétrica de GPG.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Felület a GPG szimmetrikus titkosítási funkcióihoz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Interfacie per le functionalitate de cryptation symmetric de GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Frontend untuk fungsionalitas enkripsi simetrik GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Interfaccia per la funzionalità di cifratura simmetrica di GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">GPG-ის სიმეტრიული დაშიფვრის ფუნქციონალის ინტერფეისი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">GPG의 대칭 암호화 기능 프론트엔드</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">GPG simetrinio šifravimo funkcionalumo naudotojo sąsaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Frontend voor de symmetrische versleutelingsfunctionaliteit van GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Brukarflate for funksjonalitet for symmetrisk kryptering i GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Nakładka do funkcjonalności symetrycznego szyfrowania GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Interface para a funcionalidade de encriptação simétrica do GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Interface para a funcionalidade de criptografia simétrica do GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Интерфейс для возможностей симметричного шифрования GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Frontend pre dynamické šifrovanie GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Začelje za simetrično šifriranje funkcionalnosti GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Gränssnitt för den symmetriska krypteringsfunktionaliteten i GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">GPG'nin simetrik şifreleme işlevi için ön yüz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Оболонка до можливостей з симетричного шифрування у GPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxFrontend for the symmetric encryption functionality of GPGxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">GPG 對稱加密功能的前端介面</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Symmy is a simple command-line application that nicely wraps the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Symmy és una aplicació senzilla de línia d'ordres que embolcalla la funcionalitat d'encriptatge simètric del GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Symmy és una aplicació senzilla de línia d'ordres que ajusta la funcionalitat d'encriptació simètrica de GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Symmy ist ein einfaches Befehlszeilenprogramm für die symmetrische GPG-Verschlüsselung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Symmy είναι μια απλή εφαρμογή από τη γραμμή εντολών, η οποία καλύπτει κομψά τη λειτουργία συμμετρικής κρυπτογραφίας του GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Symmy is a simple command-line application that nicely wraps the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Symmy estas simpla komandlinia aplikaĵo, kiu bele envolvas la simetrian ĉifradan funkcion de GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Symmy es una sencilla aplicación de consola para usar amigablemente la función de cifrado simétrico de GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Symmy on lihtne käsurearakendus, mis võimaldab mugavalt kasutada GPG sümmeetrilise krüptimise võimalust.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Symmy GPGren zifratze simetrikoaren funtzionaltasuna ezin hobeto biltzen duen komando-lerroko aplikazio sinple bat da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Symmy on yksinkertainen komentorivisovellus, joka paketoi GPG:n symmetrisen salaustoiminnon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Symmy est une application simple en ligne de commande qui encapsule élégamment les fonctionnalités de chiffrement symétrique de « GPG ».</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Symmy é unha aplicación sinxela da liña de ordes que expón a funcionalidade de cifraxe simétrica de GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Symmy egy egyszerű parancssori alkalmazás, amely könnyen kezelhetően csomagolja a GPG szimmetrikus titkosítási funkcióit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Simmy es un simple application de linea de commando que agradabilemente inveloppa le functionalitate de cryptation symmetric de GPS.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Symmy adalah sebuah aplikasi command-line sederhana yang mengemas secara baik si fungsionalitas enkripsi simetris GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Symmy è una semplice applicazione da riga di comando che racchiude perfettamente la funzionalità di crittografia simmetrica di GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Symmy -ი უბრალო CLI პროგრამაა, რომელიც სასიამოვნოდ ჩაატევს GPG-ის სიმეტრიული დაშიფვრის ფუნქციონალს.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Symmy는 멋지게 GPG의 대칭 암호화 기능을 래핑하는 간단한 명령행 앱입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Symmy yra paprasta komandų eilutės programa, kuri gražiai apgaubia GPG simetrinio šifravimo funkcionalumą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Symmy is een eenvoudige commandoregel toepassing die de symmetrische versleutelingsfunctionaliteit van GPG omvat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Symmy er eit kommandolinje­program for enkel tilgang GPG-funksjonane for symmetrisk kryptering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Symmy jest prostą aplikacją wiersza poleceń, która ładnie owija funkcjonalności symetrycznego szyfrowania GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Symmy é uma aplicação simples da linha de comandos que envolve de forma amigável a funcionalidade de encriptação do GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Symmy é um aplicativo em linha de comando que envolve a funcionalidade de criptografia simétrica do GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Symmy — простая программа для командной строки, представляющая собой обёртку возможностей симметричного шифрования GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Symmy je jednoduchá konzolová aplikácia ktorá pekne zalomí symetrickú funkcionalitu GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Symmy je preprosta aplikacija v ukazni vrstici, ki prijazno ponuja simetrično šifriranje funkcionalnosti GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Symmy är ett enkelt kommandoradsprogram som omsluter den symmetriska krypteringsfunktionaliteten i GPG på ett snyggt sätt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Symmy, GPG'nin simetrik şifreleme işlevini güzelce sunan bir komut satırı uygulamasıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Symmy — проста програма із інтерфейсом командного рядка, яка є зручною обгорткою до функціональних можливостей із симетричного шифрування GPG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSymmy is a simple command-line application that nicely wraps the symmetric encryption functionality of GPG.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Symmy 是一個簡單的命令列應用程式，簡化 GPG 的對稱加密功能。</p>
    <p>Symmy also provides integration with GUI file managers such as Dolphin (Encrypt and Decrypt context menu actions), as well as integration with Plasma notifications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Symmy també proporciona la integració amb els gestors de fitxers amb IGU com el Dolphin (accions de menú contextual Encripta i Desencripta), així com la integració amb les notificacions del Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Symmy també proporciona la integració amb els gestors de fitxers amb IGU com Dolphin (accions de menú contextual Encripta i Desencripta), així com la integració amb les notificacions de Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Symmy kann über die Kontextmenüeinträge Verschlüsseln/Entschlüsseln in Dateiverwaltungsprogramme wie Dolphin und in Plasma-Benachrichtigungen integriert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Symmy παρέχει και ενσωμάτωση με γραφικού περιβάλλοντος διαχειριστές αρχείων όπως το Dolphin (ενέργειες κρυπτογράφησης και αποκρυπτογράφησης), καθώς επίσης και ενσωμάτωση με τις ειδοποιήσεις Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Symmy also provides integration with GUI file managers such as Dolphin (Encrypt and Decrypt context menu actions), as well as integration with Plasma notifications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Symmy ankaŭ provizas integriĝon kun GUI-dosieradministriloj kiel Dolphin (Ĉifri kaj Malĉifri kuntekstmenuaj agoj), same kiel integriĝon kun Plasma-sciigoj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Symmy también proporciona integración con los gestores de archivos con interfaz gráfica, como Dolphin (acciones de menú de contexto «Cifrar» y «Descifrar»), así como integración con las notificaciones de Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Samuti on Symmy lõimitud graafiliste failihalduritega, nagu näiteks Dolphin (krüptimise ja lahtikrüptimise võimalused kontekstimenüüs), samuti Plasma märguannete süsteemiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Symmy, Dolphin bezalako GUI fitxategi-kudeatzaileekin bateratzen da (Zifratzea eta Deszifratzea testuinguru-menuko ekintzak), baita Plasma Jakinarazpenekin ere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Symmy tarjoaa myös integroinnin graafisiin tiedostonhallintaohjelmiin kuten Dolphiniin (Salaa- ja Pura salaus -kontekstivalikkotoiminnot) sekä Plasma-ilmoituksiin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Symmy s'intègre également aux gestionnaires de fichiers graphiques comme Dolphin (actions de menus contextuels Chiffrer et Déchiffrer), ainsi qu'aux notifications du bureau Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Symmy tamén fornece integración con xestores de ficheiros gráficos como Dolphin (as accións «Cifrar» e «Descifrar» do menú de contexto) e coas notificacións de Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Symmy további integrálódik a grafikus fájlkezelőkbe, például a Dolphinba (Titkosítás és Visszafejtés műveletek a helyi menüben), valamint a Plasma értesítéseibe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Simmy anque provide integration con gerentes de file de GUI tal como Dolphin (actiones de menu de contexto de cryptar e decryptar) tanto ben como integration con notificationes de Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Symmy juga menyediakan integrasi dengan pengelola file GUI sepertihalnya Dolphin (aksi menu konteks Enkripsi dan Dekripsi), serta integrasi dengan notifikasi Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Symmy fornisce anche un'integrazione con gestori di file grafici come Dolphin (azioni Cifra e Decifra dal menu contestuale) ed anche un'integrazione con le notifiche di Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Symmy -ს გააჩნია ჩაშენებები GUI-ის მქონე ფაილების მმართველებში, როგორიცაა Dolphn (კონტექსტურ მენიუში გაშიფვრა/დაშიფვრის პუნქტები), ისევე, როგორც Plasma-ის გაფრთხილებებთან ინტეგრაცია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">또한 Symmy는 Dolphin(암호화 및 복호화 작업 콘텍스트 메뉴)과 같은 GUI 파일 관리자와의 통합은 물론 Plasma 알림과의 통합을 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Symmy taip pat pateikia integraciją su grafinių naudotojo sąsajų failų tvarkytuvėmis, tokiomis kaip Dolphin (Šifruoti ir Iššifruoti kontekstinio meniu veiksmai), o taip pat integraciją su Plasma pranešimais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Symmy biedt ook integratie met GUI bestandsbeheerders zoals Dolphin (versleuteling- en ontcijferingacties in het contextmenu), evenals integratie met Plasma-meldingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Det er òg integrert med grafiske filhandsamarar som Dolphin (krypterings- og dekrypteringsval i kontekstmenyen) og med Plasma-varslingar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Symmy zapewnia także integrację z graficznymi przeglądarkami plików takimi jak Dolphin (menu podręczne szyfrowania i odszyfrowywania), a także z powiadomieniami Plazmy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Symmy também oferece a integração com os gestor de ficheiros gráficos, como o  Dolphin (acções do menu de contexto 'Encriptar' e 'Descodificar'), assim como a integração com as notificações do Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Symmy também fornece integração com gerenciadores de arquivos como o Dolphin (ações do menu de contexto para criptografar e descriptografar), bem como integração com as notificações do Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Symmy предусматривает интеграцию в диспетчеры файлов с графическим интерфейсом, например, в Dolphin (пункты контекстного меню «Зашифровать» и «Расшифровать»), а также интеграцию с системой уведомлений Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Symmy poskytuje aj integráciu s GUI súborovými správcami ako Dolphin (kontextové akcie šifrovanie a dešifrovanie) ako aj integráciu s Plasma pripomienkami.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Symmy omogoča tudi povezovanje z upravitelji datotek GUI, kot so Dolphin (dejanja kontekstnega menija Encrypt in Decrypt), pa tudi integracijo z obvestili v plazmi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Symmy erbjuder också integrering med grafiska filhanterare som Dolphin (sammanhangsberoende menyalternativ Kryptera och Avkryptera), samt integrering med underrättelser i Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Symmy, aynı zamanda Dolphin gibi dosya yöneticileriyle (Şifrele ve Şifre Çöz bağlam menüsü eylemleri) ve Plasma bildirimleriyle güzelce tümleşir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У Symmy передбачено можливості інтеграції до програм із графічним інтерфейсом для керування файлами, зокрема Dolphin (пункти контекстного меню «Зашифрувати» і «Розшифрувати»), а також інтеграцію із системою сповіщень Плазми.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSymmy also provides integration with GUI file managers such as Dolphin (Encrypt and Decrypt context menu actions), as well as integration with Plasma notifications.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Symmy 也提供與圖形介面檔案管理員的整合（例如 Dolphin 內文選單的加密與介面動作），以及與 Plasma 通知的整合。</p>
    <p>You can track the progress of an encryption/decryption job or kill it, using the notifications plasmoid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Podeu seguir el progrés d'un treball d'encriptatge/desencriptatge o matar-lo, utilitzant el plasmoide de les notificacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Podeu seguir el progrés d'un treball d'encriptació/desencriptació o matar-lo, utilitzant el plasmoide de les notificacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit dem Benachrichtigungs-Plasmoid können Sie eine Verschlüsselung oder Entschlüsselung überwachen oder abbrechen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Μπορείτε να παρακολουθείτε την πρόοδο μιας εργασίας (απο)κρυπτογράφησης ή να τη διαγράψετε με χρήση του πλασμοειδούς για τις ειδοποιήσεις.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">You can track the progress of an encryption/decryption job or kill it, using the notifications plasmoid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Vi povas spuri la progreson de ĉifrado/malĉifrita laboro aŭ mortigi ĝin, uzante la sciigojn plasmoidon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Puede seguir el progreso de un trabajo de cifrado o de descifrado, o matarlo, usando el plasmoide de notificaciones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Märguannete plasmoidiga saab jälgida krüptimise või lahtikrüptimise edenemist või ka vastava protsessi tappa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Zifratzeko/deszifratzeko lan baten aurrerapenaren jarraipena egin edo hura akabatu dezakezu jakinarazpenen plasmoidea erabiliz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Salaus- tai purkutyön edistymistä voi seurata tai työn tappaa ilmoitussovelmasta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Vous pouvez suivre l'avancée d'une tâche de chiffrement / déchiffrement ou l'annuler, grâce au composant graphique de notifications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Pode facer un seguimento do progreso dunha tarefa de cifraxe ou descifraxe ou cancelara mediante o trebello de notificacións.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Követheti a titkosítási és visszafejtési folyamatokat és ki is lőheti azokat az értesítések használatával.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Tu pote traciar le progresso de un labor de cryptar/decryptar o  occider lo, usante le plasmoid de notificationes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Kamu bisa melacak progres tugas enkripsi/dekripsi atau mematikannya, menggunakan plasmoid notifikasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Puoi vedere i progressi di un lavoro di cifratura o di decifratura oppure ucciderlo usando il plasmoide di notifica.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">გაფრთხილების პლაზმოიდის გამოყენებით შეგიძლიათ გაშიფვრა/დაშიფვრის პროცესს თვალი ადევნოთ, ან მოკლათ ის.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">알림 Plasmoid를 사용하여 암호화/복호화 작업의 진행 상황을 추적하거나 종료할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Galite sekti šifravimo/iššifravimo darbą arba jį nutraukti, naudodami pranešimų Plasma įskiepį.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U kunt de voortgang van een taak voor versleutelen/ontcijferen volgen of afbreken, met de plasmoid voor meldingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Du kan følgja med på (de)krypterings­prosessen eller avbryta han via medfølgjande Plasma-skjermelement.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możesz śledzić postęp zadania szyfrowania/odszyfrowywania lub je przerwać przy użyciu plazmoidu powiadomień.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Poderá seguir a evolução de uma tarefa de encriptação/descodificação ou interrompê-la, usando o plasmóide de notificações.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Você pode acompanhar o progresso da tarefa de descriptografar/criptografar ou encerrar o processo usando o plasmoide na notificação.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Плазмоид уведомлений позволяет отслеживать ход выполнения задания по шифрованию/расшифровке или прервать его.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Môžete sledovať priebeh šifrovania a dešifrovania alebo úlohu zrušiť pomocou plazmoidu notifikácií.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">S plazmoidom za obveščanja lahko sledite napredku opravila šifriranja/dešifriranja ali ga prekinete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Förloppet för krypterings- eller avkrypteringsjobb går att följa och de kan avbrytas med Plasmoiden för underrättelser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Bildirim Plasmoid'ini kullanarak şifreleme/şifre çözme işlerinin durumunu izleyebilir, onları sonlandırabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ви зможете стежити за поступом завдання із шифрування або розшифровування і переривати його за допомогою плазмоїда сповіщень.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxYou can track the progress of an encryption/decryption job or kill it, using the notifications plasmoid.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">您可以用通知 Plasma 元件來追蹤加密/解密工作的進度，或是強制中止它。</p>
  </description>
  <provides>
    <binary>symmy</binary>
  </provides>
  <update_contact>elvis.angelaccio_at_kde.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/symmy/symmy.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">security-high</icon>
</component>
